A Guide to the Records of the Policy Office: Regulations of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1990-1994
Library of Virginia
- Social Services--Voluntary Registration of Small Family Day Care Homes--Requirements for Contracting Organizations--VR 615-34-0, 1992-1993. (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Social Services--Voluntary Registration of Small Family Day Care Homes--Requirements for Providers--VR 615-35-01, 1992-1993. (Box 43, Folder 5)
- State Police--Back-up Audible Alarm Signals, 1993. (Box 43, Folder 6)
- State Police--Criminal Firearms Clearinghouse--VR 545-01-12, 1993. (Box 43, Folder 7)
- State Police--Emergency Regulations--Purchase of Handguns in Excess of One within Thirty-Day Period--Firearms Clearinghouse--VR 545-01-12, 1993. (Box 43, Folder 8)
- State Police--Motor Vehicle Safety Inspections, 1992. (Box 43, Folder 9)
- State Police--Motor Vehicle Safety Inspections--Rules and Regulations--VR 545-05-1,. (Box 43, Folder 10)
- State Police--Motor Vehicle Safety Inspections--Rules and Regulations (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 43, Folder 11)
- State Police--Motor Vehicle Safety Inspections--Rules and Regulations (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 43, Folder 12)
- State Police--Overdimensional Warning LIghts, 1993. (Box 44, Folder 1)
- State Police--Public Participation Policy--VR 545-00-01, 1992. (Box 44, Folder 2)
- State Police--Public Participation Guidelines, 1993. (Box 44, Folder 3)
- State Police--Purchase of Handguns in Excess of 1 in 30 days--VR 545-01-11, 1993. (Box 44, Folder 4)
- State Police--Regrooved or Regroovable Tires, 1993. (Box 44, Folder 5)
- State Police--Safety Lights for Farm Tractors in Excess of 108 Inches in Width, 1993. (Box 44, Folder 6)
- State Police--Stickers/Decals Used by Counties, Cities, and Towns, 1992. (Box 44, Folder 7)
- State Police--Warning Stickers or Decals for All Terrain Vehicle, 1993. (Box 44, Folder 8)
- SWCB [State Water Control Board]--VR 680-21-00, 1991-1992. (Box 44, Folder 9)
- SWCB--Aboveground Storage Tanks Pollution Prevention Requirements--VR 680-14-13, 1992-1993. (Box 44, Folder 10)
- SWCB--Corrective Action Plan General Permit--VR 680-14-11, 1992. (Box 44, Folder 11)
- SWCB--Emergency Regulations--General Permit for Domestic Sewage Discharge of less than 1,000 gallons per day, 1991. (Box 44, Folder 12)
- SWCB--Emergency Regulations--VPDES--General Permit for Storm Water Discharge Associated with Industrial Activity from Heavy Manufacturing Facilities--VR 680 14-16, 1993. (Box 45, Folder 1)
- SWCB--Emergency Regulations--VPDES--General Permit for Storm Water Discharge Associated with Industrial Activity from Transportation Facilities, Landfills Application Sites, 1993. (Box 45, Folder 2)
- SWCB--Emergency Regulations--VPDES--Permit for Nonmetallic Mineral Mining, 1993. (Box 45, Folder 3)
- SWCB--Facility and Aboveground Storage Tank Registration Requirements--VR 680-14-12, 1992-1993. (Box 45, Folder 4)
- SWCB--Facility Financial Responsibility--VR 680-14-14, 1993. (Box 45, Folder 5)
- SWCB--Fees for Permits and Certificates--VR 680-01-01, 1992. (Box 45, Folder 6)
- SWCB--General Permit Registration Statement for Storm Water Discharges Associated with Industrial Activity, 1992. (Box 45, Folder 7)
- SWCB--Ground Water Withdrawal--VR 680-13-07, 1993. (Box 45, Folder 8)
- SWCB--Oil Discharge Contingency Plan and Administrative Fees for Approval--VR 680-14-07, 1991-1992. (Box 45, Folder 9)
- SWCB--Permit for Storm Water Discharge Associated with Industrial Activities from Light Manufacturing Facilities, 1993. (Box 45, Folder 10)
- SWCB--Petroleum Underground Storage Tank Financial Responsibility--VR 680-13-03, 1992-1993. (Box 45, Folder 11)
- SWCB--Public Participation Guidelines--VR 680-41-01:1, 1992. (Box 46, Folder 1)
- SWCB--Roanoke River Basin Water Quality Management Plan--VR 680-16-02, 1991-1992. (Box 46, Folder 2)
- SWCB--Standards for Water Wells--VR 680-13-01, 1992-1993. (Box 46, Folder 3)
- SWCB--Surface Water Management Area--VR 680-15-03, 1992. (Box 46, Folder 4)
- SWCB--Tank Vessel Financial Responsibility Requirements and Administrative Fees, 1991-1992. (Box 46, Folder 5)
- SWCB--Tennessee Big Sandy River Basin Water Quality Management Plan, 1990. (Box 46, Folder 6)
- SWCB--Toxics Management--VR 680-14-03, 1990. (Box 46, Folder 7)
- SWCB--Upper James River Basin Water Quality Management Plan--VR 680-16-03, 1992-1993. (Box 46, Folder 8)
- SWCB--Upper Roanoke River Subarea Water Quality Management Plan, 1991-1992. (Box 46, Folder 9)
- SWCB--Virginia Petroleum Storage Tank Fund--VR 680-13-06, 1992-1993. (Box 47, Folder 1)
- SWCB--Virginia Pollutant Discharge Elimination System--680-14-09, 1992. (Box 47, Folder 2)
- SWCB--Virginia Pollutant Discharge Elimination System--Permit for Nonmetallic Mineral Mining--VR 680-14-20, 1993. (Box 47, Folder 3)
- SWCB--Virginia Pollutant Discharge Elimination System--Permit for Storm Water Discharge Associated with Industrial Activity, 1993. (Box 47, Folder 4)
- SWCB--Virginia Water Protection Permit--VR 680-15-02, 1992. (Box 47, Folder 5)
- SWCB--VPDES--General Permit for Storm Water Discharge Associated with Industrial Activity from Light Manufacturing Facilities, 1993. (Box 47, Folder 6)
- SWCB--VPDES--General Permit for Storm Water Discharges from Construction Sites, 1993. (Box 47, Folder 7)
- SWCB--VPDES--Permit for Storm Water Discharge from Construction Sites, 1993. (Box 47, Folder 8)
- SWCB--VPDES--Storm Water Discharge Associated with Industrial Activity from Transportation, 1993. (Box 47, Folder 9)
- SWCB--Water Protection Permit--VR 680-15-01, 1990. (Box 47, Folder 10)
- SWCB--Water Quality Standards--VR 680-21-00 (1 of 2), 1991-1992. (Box 48, Folder 1)
- SWCB--Water Quality Standards--VR 680-21-00 (2 of 2), 1991-1992. (Box 48, Folder 2)
- SWCB--Water Quality Standards--VR 680-21-00 (1 of 2), 1992. (Box 48, Folder 3)
- SWCB--Water Quality Standards--VR 680-21-00 (2 of 2), 1992. (Box 48, Folder 4)
- SWCB--Water Quality Standards--VR 680-21-00 (1 of 2), 1992-1993. (Box 48, Folder 5)
- SWCB--Water Quality Standards--VR 680-21-00 (2 of 2), 1992-1993. (Box 48, Folder 6)
- SWCB--Water Quality Standards--Town of Cleveland--VR 680-21-01.11, 1991. (Box 48, Folder 7)
- SWCB--York River Basin Water Quality Management Plan--VR 680-16-05,. (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Taxation--Consolidated and Combined Returns--VR 630-3-442, 1992-1993. (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Taxation--Corporation Income Tax: Construction Corporation Appointment--VR 63-3-419, 1993. (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Taxation--Corporation Income Tax: Foreign Sales Corporations--VR 630-3-446.1, 1992-1993. (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Taxation--Corporation Income Tax: Sales Factor--VR 630-3-414, 1993. (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Taxation--Emergency Regulations--Public Participation Guidelines, 1993. (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Taxation--Newspapers, Magazines, Periodicals, and Other Publications--VR 63-11-73, 1993. (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Taxation--Non prescription Drugs--VR 630-10-74.1, 1991-1992. (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Taxation--Nonprofit Organizations--VR 630-10-74, 1992-1993. (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Taxation--Penalties and Interest--VR 630-10-80, 1993. (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Transportation--Hazardous Materials Transportation at Bridge-Tunnel Facilities--VR 385-01-5 (1 of 2), 1992. (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Transportation--Hazardous Materials Transportation at Bridge-Tunnel Facilities--VR 385-01-5 (2 of 2), 1992. (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Transportation--Public Participation Guidelines--VR 385-01-09, 1992. (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Transportation--Underground Utility Policy, 1993. (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Transportation--Vegetation Control Regulations--VR 385-01-22, 1990-1991. (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Treasury--Emergency Regulations--Public Participation Guidelines, 1993. (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Treasury--Escheats Generally Statue--VR 640-04-1, 1992. (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Treasury--Security for Public Deposits Act--VR 640-02, 1991. (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Treasury--Security for Public Deposits Act--VR 640-02, 1993. (Box 50, Folder 1)
- VASAP [Virginia Alcohol Safety Action Program]--Policy and Procedure Manual--VR 647-01-02 (1 of 2), 1990. (Box 50, Folder 2)
- VASAP--Policy and Procedure Manual--VR 647-01-02 (2 of 2), 1990. (Box 50, Folder 3)
- VHSCRC [Virginia Health Services Cost Review Council]--Emergency Regulations--Commercial Diversification Survey, 1992. (Box 50, Folder 4)
- VHSCRC--Public Participation Guidelines--VR 370-01-001, 1992-1993. (Box 50, Folder 5)
- VHSCRC--Rules and Regulations--VR 370-01-001 (1 of 2), 1991-1993. (Box 50, Folder 6)
- VHSCRC--Rules and Regulations--VR 370-01-001 (2 of 2), 1991-1993. (Box 50, Folder 7)
- VHSCRC--Rules and Regulations--VR 370-01-001,. (Box 51, Folder 1)
- VHSCRC--Rules and Regulations--VR 370-01-001 (1 of 2),. (Box 51, Folder 2)
- VHSCRC--Rules and Regulations--VR 370-01-001 (2 of 2),. (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Waste Management--Certification of Recycling Machinery and Equipment for Tax Exemption--VR 672-50-11, 1991. (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Waste Management--Emergency Regulations--Regulated Medical Waste Management, 1993. (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Waste Management--Public Participation Guidelines--VR 672-01-1:1, 1992-1993. (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Waste Management--Solid Waste Management Facility Permit Application--VR 672-20-11, 1991-1993. (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Waste Management--Transportation of Hazardous Materials, 1990-1993. (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Waste Management--Yard Waste Com posting Facility--VR 672-20-32, 1991. (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Youth and Family Services--Certification Process--VR 690-10-001, 1992. (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Youth and Family Services--Learning Center Standards, 1992. (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Youth and Family Services--Pre and Post-Dispositional Group Home Standard--VR 690-02-001, 1991. (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Youth and Family Services--Public Participation Guidelines--VR 690-01-001, 1990. (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Youth and Family Services--Public Participation Guidelines, 1990-1991. (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Youth and Family Services--Standards for Secure Detention Homes--VR 690-30-001, 1991-1992. (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Youth and Family Services--State Reimbursement of Local Juvenile Residential Facilities Construction Cost, 1992. (Box 52, Folder 10)